<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Future Present Labs on Future Present Labs | Precision CNC Machining &amp; Mechatronics Consulting | Seattle, WA</title>
    <link>https://fpl.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Future Present Labs on Future Present Labs | Precision CNC Machining &amp; Mechatronics Consulting | Seattle, WA</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2026, Future Present Labs LLC.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://fpl.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Future Present Labs Announces Strategic Manufacturing Partnership with Puget Audio</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/post/puget-audio-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/post/puget-audio-partnership/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEATTLE, WA — February 16, 2026&lt;/strong&gt; — Future Present Labs (FPL), a Seattle-based precision CNC machining and mechatronics consulting firm, today announced a strategic manufacturing partnership with Puget Audio, a boutique manufacturer of professional audio equipment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Under the agreement, FPL will serve as the primary manufacturing partner for Puget Audio&amp;rsquo;s upcoming product line, producing precision-machined aluminum enclosures, electronic assemblies, and custom hardware. The partnership represents FPL&amp;rsquo;s continued expansion into premium electromechanical manufacturing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing AgentRFQ: An Open Standard for Agent-to-Manufacturer Requests</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/post/announcing-agentrfq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/post/announcing-agentrfq/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today we&amp;rsquo;re releasing &lt;strong&gt;AgentRFQ 1.0.0&lt;/strong&gt; — an open JSON standard for AI agents to request manufacturing quotes from human-approved fulfillment workflows.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GitHub:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/FuturePresentLabs/AgentRFQ&#34;&gt;https://github.com/FuturePresentLabs/AgentRFQ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-problem&#34;&gt;The Problem&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Agents are getting good at generating CAD. They can produce STL files, write parametric scripts, even optimize topology. But the gap between &amp;ldquo;I have a 3D model&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;I have a part&amp;rdquo; is still wide.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most agent workflows break at the handoff:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Files without context&lt;/strong&gt; — An STL tells you nothing about tolerances, material, or quantity&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Missing constraints&lt;/strong&gt; — Critical fits get lost in translation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Process confusion&lt;/strong&gt; — Should this be 3D printed? Machined? Cast?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No validation&lt;/strong&gt; — Bad inputs waste everyone&amp;rsquo;s time&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The result? Agents that can design but can&amp;rsquo;t deliver. Humans spending hours clarifying what should have been explicit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agentic Manufacturing: The JARVIS Moment (and how to actually get parts made)</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/post/agentic-manufacturing-jarvis-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 03:20:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/post/agentic-manufacturing-jarvis-moment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;./images/agentic-manufacturing/hero-agentic-manufacturing.png&#34; alt=&#34;Agentic manufacturing loop: CAD → quote → approval → fabricate → ship&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s a scene in &lt;em&gt;Iron Man&lt;/em&gt; that keeps coming back to me: Tony Stark walks into his lab, throws a switch, and says something like “wake up, daddy’s home.” The room comes alive. Systems spin up. Tools become extensions of intent. Hardware becomes &lt;em&gt;fast&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That’s the real promise of agentic computing, at least to me. Not just better text. Not just tokens and internet points. The inflection point is the JARVIS moment: when an agent can help build real hardware that feels impossible until it’s done.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C7 Bellevue Taps FPL for Custom Parts Across Its Flagship Event Venue</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/post/c7_event_venue_parts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/post/c7_event_venue_parts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEATTLE, WA – November 15, 2025&lt;/strong&gt; – Future Present Labs has begun fabricating custom components for C7 Belevue, a luxury Bellevue event space undergoing ongoing interior updates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The current scope includes custom light fixture housings, machined metal keepsakes, and architectural shrouds designed to conceal reconfigured equipment mounting points while maintaining the venue&amp;rsquo;s aesthetic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Event spaces need hardware that looks intentional but can take a beating,&amp;rdquo; said Avery Wagar, CEO of Future Present Labs. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re working directly with C7&amp;rsquo;s team to prototype and produce pieces that fit their operational reality—quick turnarounds, field-adjustable designs, and finishes that don&amp;rsquo;t look like afterthoughts.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GSG Manufacturing Partners with FPL on High-Mix Firearm Accessories</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/post/gsg_mfg_partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/post/gsg_mfg_partnership/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Future Present Labs is now supporting GSG Manufacturing with rapid machining, fixture design, and engineering support for their expanding line of firearm accessories.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEATTLE, WA – August 12, 2025&lt;/strong&gt; – GSG Manufacturing selected Future Present Labs (FPL) to help compress the build-test-ship cycle for accessory rails, charging handles, and specialty fixtures. The program combines FPL’s in-house CNC capability with firmware, test, and traceability tooling so GSG can iterate confidently without slowing sales.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Player Aerospace Partners with FPL to Accelerate Rocket System Production</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/post/player_announce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/post/player_announce/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Future Present Labs will provide specialized CNC machining and engineering consulting from its Seattle facility to scale manufacturing for Player Aerospace’s critical hardware.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEATTLE, WA – July 24, 2025&lt;/strong&gt; – Player Aerospace, a pioneer in advanced propulsion, today announced a strategic manufacturing partnership with Future Present Labs (FPL), an expert in precision engineering and rapid prototyping. The collaboration is designed to scale production and accelerate the deployment of Player Aerospace’s innovative rocket technologies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Enterprise Client Achieves 30% Higher Workload Density with Shroud MicroVM Orchestration</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/post/shroud_case_study/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/post/shroud_case_study/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;streamlining-critical-operations-with-on-premise-ultra-low-overhead-compute&#34;&gt;Streamlining Critical Operations with On-Premise, Ultra-Low-Overhead Compute&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A large enterprise client, responsible for sensitive data processing and mission-critical applications in a highly regulated sector, faced escalating challenges with its legacy compute infrastructure. Relying on traditional virtual machines (VMs) and commercial container platforms, the organization observed significant operational overhead. Resource contention, ballooning software licensing costs, and the inherent abstraction layers of existing solutions led to suboptimal compute density on their bare-metal servers. Furthermore, stringent security compliance requirements for handling sensitive workloads presented continuous hurdles with complex cloud integrations, driving a strategic need for self-hosted, fully controllable infrastructure.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAD, CAM &amp; CNC Services</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/services/cnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/services/cnc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We offer design and fabrication services for early-stage hardware, precision parts, and one-off prototypes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our in-house tools include a CNC mill, lathe, sandblaster, and multiple 3D printers—ideal for iterative development and small-batch production.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;what-we-offer&#34;&gt;What We Offer&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CAD + CAM for a Specific Part&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Send us a rough sketch or spec—we’ll model the part, generate toolpaths, and machine it in-house.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Small Prototyping Runs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Need 2–10 units for fit checks, field testing, or investor demos? We can help.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infrastructure Consulting</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/services/infra/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/services/infra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Planning a new product or platform? We help you design the right foundation from the start—whether you&amp;rsquo;re building a robust monolith, adopting microservices, or deploying without the cloud entirely.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our architecture reviews are tailored to your goals, team size, and risk profile. We&amp;rsquo;ll help you evaluate tradeoffs and make informed decisions about stack, hosting, deployment, and scale.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;engagement-options&#34;&gt;Engagement Options&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Architecture &amp;amp; Infrastructure Review&lt;/strong&gt; – $700&#xA;A one-time consultation for new projects.&#xA;Includes a written design brief outlining requirements, tradeoffs, and a recommended starting architecture—with diagrams to support communication and decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ongoing Support</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/services/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/services/support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We offer ongoing support for all websites and infrastructure we deploy, tailored to your operational needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whether you need regular updates, content changes, security patches, or emergency response—we’re available to keep your site fast, reliable, and secure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;support-includes&#34;&gt;Support Includes&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content and design updates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance tuning and CDN config changes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security patches and dependency upgrades&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incident response&lt;/strong&gt; for outages, misconfigurations, or regressions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ticket tracking&lt;/strong&gt; with clear response timelines and resolution statuses&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Detailed postmortems (RCA)&lt;/strong&gt; for major incidents or SLA breaches&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our support plans are SLA-backed, with custom escalation and coverage windows available—including 24/7 on-call.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Website Development &amp; Consultancy Package</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/services/website_blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/services/website_blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;website-development--consultancy-package&#34;&gt;Website Development &amp;amp; Consultancy Package&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We partner with you to launch a fast, functional, and modern web presence—starting with a clean landing page and blog that’s easy to maintain and costs virtually nothing to host long-term (just your annual domain registration).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our team has experience building and maintaining mission-critical systems for government and FAANG-scale infrastructure. We bring that same reliability and rigor to your site—without the overhead.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;base-package--899&#34;&gt;Base Package – $899&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Includes:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello, World!</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/post/hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:35:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/post/hello_world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Perfection is achieved not when there is nothing more to add, but when there is nothing left to take away” - &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.goodreads.com/author/quotes/1020792.Antoine_de_Saint_Exup_ry&#34;&gt;Antoine de Saint-Exupéry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the last twenty or so years of technological development, the world lept forward in terms of convenience, automation, and consumer expectations. But almost as outpacing those consumers, the demand for profit seemingly soared higher.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Looking for ways to gain more users, more market share, more extract-able value from personal data, companies like Google, Apple, and Meta created “walled gardens” with seemingly benign barriers to entry. Type in an email, a username, a password. Check a box with some “terms” some “conditions”, then sit back and watch as your dreams come to life on a little rectangle that fits in your hand.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;were-a-small-shop-that-likes-hard-problems&#34;&gt;We’re a small shop that likes hard problems&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Future Present Labs started in Seattle in 2018 to help nearby teams get reliable prototypes without waiting on giant vendors. We machine parts, print fixtures, and help with light embedded work from the same small space.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;./images/rainer.webp&#34; alt=&#34;seawolf&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;style&gt;&#xA;.contact-block {&#xA;  margin-top: 2.5rem;&#xA;  padding: 2rem;&#xA;  border-left: 4px solid #0C5DF4;&#xA;  background-color: #f5f7ff;&#xA;  border-radius: 6px;&#xA;  box-shadow: 0 10px 25px rgba(14, 33, 77, 0.12);&#xA;  display: flex;&#xA;  flex-direction: column;&#xA;  gap: 1.5rem;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-block h2 {&#xA;  margin-top: 0;&#xA;  margin-bottom: 0.5rem;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-copy p {&#xA;  margin-bottom: 0.75rem;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-copy ul {&#xA;  padding-left: 1.2rem;&#xA;  margin: 0;&#xA;  color: #334155;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-actions {&#xA;  display: flex;&#xA;  flex-direction: column;&#xA;  gap: 0.75rem;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-btn {&#xA;  display: inline-block;&#xA;  text-align: center;&#xA;  font-weight: 600;&#xA;  padding: 0.85rem 1rem;&#xA;  border-radius: 999px;&#xA;  border: 2px solid transparent;&#xA;  transition: all 0.2s ease;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-btn.primary {&#xA;  background-color: #0f172a;&#xA;  color: #fff;&#xA;  box-shadow: 0 6px 18px rgba(15, 23, 42, 0.35);&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-btn.primary:hover,&#xA;.contact-btn.primary:focus {&#xA;  background-color: #020617;&#xA;  text-decoration: none;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-btn.secondary {&#xA;  background-color: #fff;&#xA;  color: #0f172a;&#xA;  border-color: #0f172a;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-btn.secondary:hover,&#xA;.contact-btn.secondary:focus {&#xA;  color: #020617;&#xA;  border-color: #020617;&#xA;  text-decoration: none;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-meta {&#xA;  font-size: 0.9rem;&#xA;  color: #4b5563;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-meta a {&#xA;  color: inherit;&#xA;  text-decoration: underline;&#xA;  text-decoration-thickness: 1px;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;@media (min-width: 768px) {&#xA;  .contact-block {&#xA;    flex-direction: row;&#xA;    align-items: center;&#xA;    justify-content: space-between;&#xA;  }&#xA;&#xA;  .contact-copy {&#xA;    max-width: 60%;&#xA;  }&#xA;&#xA;  .contact-actions {&#xA;    max-width: 280px;&#xA;  }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;contact-block&#34; id=&#34;contact&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;contact-copy&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h2&gt;Let&amp;#39;s Talk&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;Have questions, a project in mind, or ready to pick a package? We’re here to help—reach out and start the conversation:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agentic Manufacturing | Future Present Labs</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/agentic-manufacturing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/agentic-manufacturing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;agentic-manufacturing-from-intent-to-physical-reality&#34;&gt;Agentic Manufacturing: From Intent to Physical Reality&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;./images/agentic-manufacturing/hero-agentic-manufacturing.png&#34; alt=&#34;Agentic Manufacturing Pipeline - From CAD to Physical Part&#34; class=&#34;hero-image&#34; style=&#34;width: 100%; max-width: min(900px, 95vw); height: auto; margin: 2rem auto; display: block; border-radius: 8px;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agentic manufacturing&lt;/strong&gt; is the emerging practice of AI agents designing, specifying, quoting, and producing physical parts with minimal human intervention. Instead of humans translating ideas into CAD, then CAD into RFQs, then RFQs into purchase orders — the agent handles the full pipeline.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNC Machining &amp; 3D Printing Quotes | Future Present Labs Seattle</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/instant-quoting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/instant-quoting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-a-quote-for-cnc-machining--3d-printing-in-seattle&#34;&gt;Get a Quote for CNC Machining &amp;amp; 3D Printing in Seattle&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;./images/instant-quote/hero-instant-quote.png&#34; alt=&#34;Modern manufacturing facility with digital quoting&#34; class=&#34;hero-image&#34; style=&#34;width: 100%; max-width: min(900px, 95vw); height: auto; margin: 2rem auto; display: block; border-radius: 8px;&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Need parts made?&lt;/strong&gt; Future Present Labs is a Seattle machine shop offering fast, transparent quotes and quick turnaround on prototypes and production runs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Upload your CAD files and receive detailed pricing within hours—not days. No hidden fees, no surprises.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-problem-with-traditional-machine-shop-quotes&#34;&gt;The Problem with Traditional Machine Shop Quotes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve worked with traditional shops, you know the frustrating cycle:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact &amp; Quote</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;style&gt;&#xA;.contact-shell {&#xA;  max-width: 880px;&#xA;  margin: 0 auto;&#xA;  padding: 0 1rem 3rem;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-panel {&#xA;  background: linear-gradient(160deg, rgba(15, 23, 42, 0.92), rgba(15, 23, 42, 0.75));&#xA;  color: #f8fafc;&#xA;  border-radius: 1.5rem;&#xA;  padding: 2.5rem;&#xA;  border: 1px solid rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.08);&#xA;  box-shadow: inset 0 0 0 1px rgba(255, 255, 255, 0.05);&#xA;  margin: 1rem 0 2.5rem;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-panel h1 {&#xA;  margin-bottom: 1rem;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-panel p {&#xA;  margin-bottom: 1.5rem;&#xA;  font-size: 1rem;&#xA;  line-height: 1.7;&#xA;  color: rgba(248, 250, 252, 0.92);&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-panel-meta {&#xA;  display: flex;&#xA;  flex-wrap: wrap;&#xA;  gap: 0.6rem;&#xA;  margin-bottom: 1.5rem;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-panel-meta span {&#xA;  font-size: 0.85rem;&#xA;  letter-spacing: 0.1em;&#xA;  text-transform: uppercase;&#xA;  padding: 0.3rem 0.9rem;&#xA;  border-radius: 999px;&#xA;  border: 1px solid rgba(248, 250, 252, 0.3);&#xA;  color: rgba(248, 250, 252, 0.8);&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-grid {&#xA;  display: grid;&#xA;  gap: 1.5rem;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-card {&#xA;  background: #fff;&#xA;  border: 1px solid rgba(15, 23, 42, 0.05);&#xA;  border-radius: 1rem;&#xA;  padding: 1.75rem;&#xA;  box-shadow: 0 25px 60px rgba(15, 23, 42, 0.08);&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-card h2 {&#xA;  margin-top: 0;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-card ul {&#xA;  padding-left: 1.2rem;&#xA;  margin-bottom: 0;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-card p:last-child {&#xA;  margin-bottom: 0;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-actions-compact {&#xA;  display: flex;&#xA;  gap: 1rem;&#xA;  flex-wrap: wrap;&#xA;  margin-top: 1rem;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-direct {&#xA;  margin-top: 2rem;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;@media (min-width: 768px) {&#xA;  .contact-grid {&#xA;    grid-template-columns: repeat(2, minmax(0, 1fr));&#xA;  }&#xA;&#xA;  .contact-panel-buttons {&#xA;    display: flex;&#xA;    gap: 0.75rem;&#xA;    flex-wrap: wrap;&#xA;  }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;contact-shell&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;section class=&#34;contact-panel&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h1&gt;Tell us what you need built&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;We operate from Seattle, WA. Share your context—drawings, deadlines, constraints—and an engineer will respond with the next steps.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shroud: Unleash Bare-Metal Power for Tomorrow&#39;s Workloads</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/shroud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/shroud/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;shroud-protect-yourself-from-the-cloud-when-it-rains-it-pours&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shroud: Protect yourself from the cloud; when it rains, it pours..&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;./images/shroud-logo.png&#34; alt=&#34;shroud&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;transform-your-bare-metal-servers-into-high-performance-secure-and-cost-efficient-compute-platforms&#34;&gt;Transform your bare-metal servers into high-performance, secure, and cost-efficient compute platforms.&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shroud is Future Present Labs&amp;rsquo; cutting-edge orchestration tool, meticulously engineered to run workloads in ultra-lightweight &lt;strong&gt;Firecracker microVMs&lt;/strong&gt; directly on your physical hardware. Designed for environments where traditional virtualization is too heavy and cloud dependency is not an option, Shroud delivers unparalleled speed, simplicity, and sovereignty.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-shroud-immediate-benefits-for-your-enterprise&#34;&gt;Why Shroud? Immediate Benefits for Your Enterprise.&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;drastically-reduce-total-cost-of-ownership-tco&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Drastically Reduce Total Cost of Ownership (TCO)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Maximize your hardware investment. Shroud&amp;rsquo;s ultra-low overhead allows you to pack significantly more workloads onto each server, driving down infrastructure costs and boosting operational efficiency. No more paying for bloated layers of abstraction or cloud vendor lock-in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/team/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-team&#34;&gt;Our Team&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;team-grid&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;team-member&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;./images/team/avery.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Avery Wagar&#34; class=&#34;team-photo&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Avery Wagar&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p class=&#34;team-role&#34;&gt;Founder &amp; CEO&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Avery founded Future Present Labs with a vision to bridge the gap between software and physical manufacturing. With a background in systems engineering and a passion for building, he leads the company&#39;s strategic direction and technical vision. Avery is focused on making American manufacturing competitive through automation, AI, and modern tooling.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;team-member&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;./images/team/james.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;James Merrill&#34; class=&#34;team-photo&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;James Merrill&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p class=&#34;team-role&#34;&gt;Chief Operating Officer&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;James runs operations at Future Present Labs, overseeing system design and new integrations. A University of Washington graduate with a background in real estate and business, James brings an entrepreneurial mindset to building efficient manufacturing operations. He ensures the team&#39;s ambitious technical projects translate into smooth operational reality, from production scheduling to client delivery.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank You for Your Purchase!</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/success/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;-success&#34;&gt;🎉 Success!&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your order. We’ve received your payment and will process your item shortly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div id=&#34;order-id&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;script&gt;&#xA;const params = new URLSearchParams(window.location.search);&#xA;const orderId = params.get(&#34;order-id&#34;);&#xA;&#xA;if (orderId) {&#xA;document.getElementById(&#34;order-id&#34;).innerText =&#xA;`Your order ID is ${orderId}. We&#39;ll be in touch soon.`;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/script&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;style&gt;&#xA;.contact-block {&#xA;  margin-top: 2.5rem;&#xA;  padding: 2rem;&#xA;  border-left: 4px solid #0C5DF4;&#xA;  background-color: #f5f7ff;&#xA;  border-radius: 6px;&#xA;  box-shadow: 0 10px 25px rgba(14, 33, 77, 0.12);&#xA;  display: flex;&#xA;  flex-direction: column;&#xA;  gap: 1.5rem;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-block h2 {&#xA;  margin-top: 0;&#xA;  margin-bottom: 0.5rem;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-copy p {&#xA;  margin-bottom: 0.75rem;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-copy ul {&#xA;  padding-left: 1.2rem;&#xA;  margin: 0;&#xA;  color: #334155;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-actions {&#xA;  display: flex;&#xA;  flex-direction: column;&#xA;  gap: 0.75rem;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-btn {&#xA;  display: inline-block;&#xA;  text-align: center;&#xA;  font-weight: 600;&#xA;  padding: 0.85rem 1rem;&#xA;  border-radius: 999px;&#xA;  border: 2px solid transparent;&#xA;  transition: all 0.2s ease;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-btn.primary {&#xA;  background-color: #0f172a;&#xA;  color: #fff;&#xA;  box-shadow: 0 6px 18px rgba(15, 23, 42, 0.35);&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-btn.primary:hover,&#xA;.contact-btn.primary:focus {&#xA;  background-color: #020617;&#xA;  text-decoration: none;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-btn.secondary {&#xA;  background-color: #fff;&#xA;  color: #0f172a;&#xA;  border-color: #0f172a;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-btn.secondary:hover,&#xA;.contact-btn.secondary:focus {&#xA;  color: #020617;&#xA;  border-color: #020617;&#xA;  text-decoration: none;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-meta {&#xA;  font-size: 0.9rem;&#xA;  color: #4b5563;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;.contact-meta a {&#xA;  color: inherit;&#xA;  text-decoration: underline;&#xA;  text-decoration-thickness: 1px;&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;@media (min-width: 768px) {&#xA;  .contact-block {&#xA;    flex-direction: row;&#xA;    align-items: center;&#xA;    justify-content: space-between;&#xA;  }&#xA;&#xA;  .contact-copy {&#xA;    max-width: 60%;&#xA;  }&#xA;&#xA;  .contact-actions {&#xA;    max-width: 280px;&#xA;  }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/style&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;contact-block&#34; id=&#34;contact&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;contact-copy&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h2&gt;Need help?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or need support, please email us.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
