<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Partnerships on Future Present Labs | Precision CNC Machining &amp; Mechatronics Consulting | Seattle, WA</title>
    <link>https://fpl.dev/categories/partnerships/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Partnerships on Future Present Labs | Precision CNC Machining &amp; Mechatronics Consulting | Seattle, WA</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2026, Future Present Labs LLC.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://fpl.dev/categories/partnerships/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Puget Audio Taps Future Present Labs for Manufacturing Partnership</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/post/puget-audio-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/post/puget-audio-partnership/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEATTLE, WA — February 16, 2026&lt;/strong&gt; — Puget Audio has tapped Future Present Labs (FPL) to manufacture their upcoming line of analog FX pedals. FPL will handle DFM, CNC drilling and milling on standard 125B enclosures, PCB integration, final assembly, and in-house Cerakote finishing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-fpl-is-handling&#34;&gt;What FPL Is Handling&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DFM &amp;amp; Machining&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Working from Puget Audio&amp;rsquo;s designs, FPL is providing DFM feedback and machining standard 125B aluminum enclosures: drilling for pots, jacks, and footswitch, plus any pocketing needed for battery clearance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C7 Bellevue Taps FPL for Custom Parts Across Its Flagship Event Venue</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/post/c7_event_venue_parts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/post/c7_event_venue_parts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEATTLE, WA – November 15, 2025&lt;/strong&gt; – Future Present Labs has begun fabricating custom components for C7 Belevue, a luxury Bellevue event space undergoing ongoing interior updates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The current scope includes custom light fixture housings, machined metal keepsakes, and architectural shrouds designed to conceal reconfigured equipment mounting points while maintaining the venue&amp;rsquo;s aesthetic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Event spaces need hardware that looks intentional but can take a beating,&amp;rdquo; said Avery Wagar, CEO of Future Present Labs. &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re working directly with C7&amp;rsquo;s team to prototype and produce pieces that fit their operational reality—quick turnarounds, field-adjustable designs, and finishes that don&amp;rsquo;t look like afterthoughts.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GSG Manufacturing Partners with FPL on High-Mix Firearm Accessories</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/post/gsg_mfg_partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/post/gsg_mfg_partnership/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Future Present Labs is now supporting GSG Manufacturing with rapid machining, fixture design, and engineering support for their expanding line of firearm accessories.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEATTLE, WA – August 12, 2025&lt;/strong&gt; – GSG Manufacturing selected Future Present Labs (FPL) to help compress the build-test-ship cycle for accessory rails, charging handles, and specialty fixtures. The program combines FPL’s in-house CNC capability with firmware, test, and traceability tooling so GSG can iterate confidently without slowing sales.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Player Aerospace Partners with FPL to Accelerate Rocket System Production</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/post/player_announce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/post/player_announce/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Future Present Labs will provide specialized CNC machining and engineering consulting from its Seattle facility to scale manufacturing for Player Aerospace’s critical hardware.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEATTLE, WA – July 24, 2025&lt;/strong&gt; – Player Aerospace, a pioneer in advanced propulsion, today announced a strategic manufacturing partnership with Future Present Labs (FPL), an expert in precision engineering and rapid prototyping. The collaboration is designed to scale production and accelerate the deployment of Player Aerospace’s innovative rocket technologies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
