<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manufacturing on Future Present Labs | Precision CNC Machining &amp; Mechatronics Consulting | Seattle, WA</title>
    <link>https://fpl.dev/categories/manufacturing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Manufacturing on Future Present Labs | Precision CNC Machining &amp; Mechatronics Consulting | Seattle, WA</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2026, Future Present Labs LLC.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:00:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://fpl.dev/categories/manufacturing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Future Present Labs Partners with Puget Audio to Manufacture Premium FX Pedal Line</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/post/puget-audio-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/post/puget-audio-partnership/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEATTLE, WA — February 16, 2026&lt;/strong&gt; — Future Present Labs (FPL), a Seattle-based precision CNC machining and mechatronics consulting firm, today announced a strategic manufacturing partnership with &lt;a href=&#34;https://puget.audio&#34;&gt;Puget Audio&lt;/a&gt;, an emerging boutique audio equipment manufacturer specializing in analog FX pedals for guitar and bass.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Under the agreement, FPL will serve as the primary manufacturing partner for Puget Audio&amp;rsquo;s debut pedal line, which includes three flagship products: The Overdrive ($149), The Fuzz ($129), and The Delay ($179). The pedals feature handwired analog circuitry with premium components, true bypass switching, and rugged enclosures built to withstand the demands of touring musicians.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agentic Manufacturing: The JARVIS Moment (and how to actually get parts made)</title>
      <link>https://fpl.dev/post/agentic-manufacturing-jarvis-moment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 03:20:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fpl.dev/post/agentic-manufacturing-jarvis-moment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;../../images/agentic-manufacturing/hero-agentic-manufacturing.png&#34; alt=&#34;Agentic manufacturing loop: CAD → quote → approval → fabricate → ship&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There’s a scene in &lt;em&gt;Iron Man&lt;/em&gt; that keeps coming back to me: Tony Stark walks into his lab, throws a switch, and says something like “wake up, daddy’s home.” The room comes alive. Systems spin up. Tools become extensions of intent. Hardware becomes &lt;em&gt;fast&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That’s the real promise of agentic computing, at least to me. Not just better text. Not just tokens and internet points. The inflection point is the JARVIS moment: when an agent can help build real hardware that feels impossible until it’s done.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
